Library of Congress and Fisk University Mississippi Delta collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Sound Recordings, 97 sound discs
  - AFS 06626, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side B
      - 3. The Big Mosquitoes (story), July 23, 1942
        Unidentified performer.
      - 4. The Man who Walked the Water Liked Christ (story), July 23, 1942
      - 5. The White Doctor and his Servants (story), July 23, 1942
  - AFS 06627, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      Performed by "Buck Asa" Ulysses Jefferson.
      - 1. John Loses the Race (story), July 23, 1942
      - 2. John (Jack) Guesses What is Under the Pot (story), July 23, 1942
      - 3. John and the Lord (story), July 23, 1942
      - 4. The Preacher and his Hogs (story), July 23, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. The Preacher and his Hogs (story, concluded), July 23, 1942
      - 2. The Swift Peter (story), July 23, 1942
      - 3. The Preacher Who Always Could Be Trapped, by Pussy (story), July 23, 1942
      - 4. The Women Who Couldn't Count (story), July 23, 1942
      - 5. The Lady and Her Three Daughters (story), July 23, 1942
      - 6. Bring Me My "Duck" (story, incomplete), July 23, 1942
  - AFS 06628, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A Tracks 1-3 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Nelson Funeral Home in Clarksdale, Mississippi. Side A Tracks 6-8 and Side B recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Stovall, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. White Man, Jew and Negro Go to Heaven (story), July 23, 1942
      - 2. The Ox and Mule (story), July 23, 1942
      - 3. The Jew and the Irishman at the Cemetery (story), July 23, 1942
      - 4. Test
      - 5. Test
      - 6. Ramblin' Kid Blues, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Muddy Waters (McKinley Morganfield), Percy Thomas, Son Simms, and Louis Ford.
      - 7. Rosalie, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Muddy Waters, Percy Thomas, Son Simms, and Louis Ford.
      - 8. Joe Turner Blues, July 24, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Pearlie May Blues, July 24, 1942
      - 2. Take a Walk with Me, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Muddy Waters and Son Simms.
      - 3. Burr Clover Blues, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Muddy Waters (McKinley Morganfield).
  - AFS 06629, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Stovall, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. I Be Bound to Write to You, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Muddy Waters (McKinley Morganfield) and Charles Berry.
      - 2. I Be Bound to Write to You, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Muddy Waters and Charles Berry.
      - 3. You Gonna Miss Me When I'm Dead and Gone, July 24, 1942
      - 4. Corn Field Holler, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Charles Berry.
      - 5. Pitch Pipe, July 24, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Cornfield Holler, July 24, 1942
      - 2. Test
      - 3. Joe Turner Blues, July 24, 1942
        Performed by Son Simms.
      - 4. Test
  - AFS 06630, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Asa Ware and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Hobson Plantation in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Three Suitors Who Were Fast Men (story), July 25, 1942
      - 2. The Foolish Boy and the Preachers (story), July 25, 1942
      - 3. Greensnake (story), July 25, 1942
      - 4. Interview Bud Doggett, July 25, 1942
    - Side B
      - Tests
  - AFS 06631
    - Side A, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
      - 1. Mr. Bear and Mr. Rabbitt (story), 1942
      - 2. Mr. Bear and Mr. Rabbitt (story), 1942
      - 3. Three Sons Look for their Fortunes (story), 1942
      - 4. The Woman Who Never Had No Man (story), 1942
      - 5. Git up in the Mornin' Soon, 1942
      - 6. Casey Jones (fragment), 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06631b
      - 1. Levee Camp Song, 1942
      - 2. Bud Doggett Toast, 1942
        Performed by Will Starks.
      - 3. Preacher and the Lady, 1942
      - 4. Levee Camp Song, 1942
      - 5. Levee Camp Song, 1942
      - 6. Levee Camp Song, 1942
      - 7. The Devil Counts Souls in the Graveyard, 1942
  - AFS 06632, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Hobson Plantation in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06632a
      Performed by Asa Ware.
      - 1. Man Runs Away from the Gunshot (story), 1942
      - 2. The Lawyer, Bookkeeper and the Tramp Go to Mary (story), 1942
      - 3. The Chicken Stealin' Man (story), 1942
      - 4. Test
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06632b
      - 1. The Queen of Africa, 1942
        Performed by O.C. King.
      - 2. Shine and the Titanic, 1942
      - 3. Toast about Preachers, 1942
      - 4. The Railroad Men Go to Town, 1942
      - 5. The Animals Have a Convention, 1942
      - 6. The Lady Washing at the Spring, 1942
      - 7. Stewball, 1942
      - 8. Test
  - AFS 06633
    - Side A, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.; afc1941002_afs06633a
      Side A Tracks 1-5 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Hobson Plantation in Clarksdale, Mississippi. Side A Track 6 and Side B recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Church of God in Christ with Rev. McGhee in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
      - 1. Frankie and Albert, 1942
      - 2. Frankie and Albert, 1942
      - 3. Blank
      - 4. Test
      - 5. When I Shall Wear the Golden Crown, 1942
      - 6. Opening Prayer, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06633b
      - 1. Do Remember Me, 1942
      - 2. Testimony, 1942
      - 3. I'll Live On, 1942
      - 4. Testimony, 1942
      - 5. I'm Pressing On, 1942
      - 6. Testimony, 1942
      - 7. Every Hour I'm with You, 1942
      - 8. Testimony, 1942
      - 9. Jesus is My Friend, 1942
      - 10. Testimony, 1942
      - 11. With Angels Climbin' the Golden Stairs, 1942
  - AFS 06634, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Rev. McGhee and congregation of the Church of God in Christ and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. I Got a Heaven in My View, 1942
      - 2. Testimony, 1942
      - 3. I Got a Heaven in My View, 1942
      - 4. If You Put Yo' Trust in Jesus, Everything Will Be All Right, 1942
      - 5. Testimony, 1942
      - 6. Talk - Visiting Pastor, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06634b
      - 1. Sacramental Sermon, 1942
      - 2. At the Cross Where I First Saw the Light, 1942
      - 3. Talk, 1942
      - 4. Yea, Lawd, 1942
  - AFS 06635, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Yes, Lord, 1942
      - 2. Sacramental Text, 1942
      - 3. The Blood Have Made Me Whole, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06635b
      - 1. Prayer, 1942
      - 2. Yes, Lord, 1942
      - 3. Praise Him, 1942
      - 4. I'm Running for my Life, 1942
      - 5. Talk on Footwashing, 1942
  - AFS 06636, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06636a
      - 1. Talk on Footwashing, 1942
      - 2. He never Said a Mumbalin' Word, 1942
      - 3. Peter, as the Years Go By, 1942
      - 4. Everybody Get on Board, 1942
      - 5. Just Like Heaven to Me, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06636b
      - 1. Unidentified, 1942
      - 2. Unidentified, 1942
  - AFS 06637, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A and Side B Track 1 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Clarksdale, Mississippi. Side B Tracks 2-5 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Silent Grove Baptist Church in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06637a
      Performed by Rev. McGhee and congregation of the Church of God in Christ.
      - 1. I'm a Soldier in the Army of My Lord, 1942
      - 2. Lighting the Offering, 1942
      - 3. Every Little Talk with Jesus Makes it Right, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06637b
      - 1. Jesus is My Everything, 1942
      - 2. Just a Closer Walk With Thee, 1942
      - 3. I Been the Cryin', 1942
      - 4. The Usher, 1942
        Recited by Ella Mae Williams
      - 5. I'm Sending Up My Timber to Heaven Every Day, 1942
  - AFS 06638, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Silent Grove Baptist Church in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06638a
      - 1. You Just Sing for Jesus, 1942
        Performed by the Four Stars Quartet.
      - 2. My Lawd So High You Can't Go Over Him, 1942
        Performed by the Union Jubilee Quartet.
      - 3. Please Don't Drive Me Away, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06638b
      - 1. Christ My Lord is Coming Soon, 1942
      - 2. Jesus Knows All About It, 1942
        Performed by Connie Barmore.
  - AFS 06639, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Precious Lord, 1942
      - 2. Thru the Years We Keep on Toiling, 1942
      - 3. The Holy Baby, 1942
    - Side B
      Performed by Bozie Sturdevant.
      - 1. Ain't No Grave Can Hold My Body Down, 1942
      - 2. When I've Done the Best I Can, I Want My Crown, 1942
  - AFS 06640, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06640a
      - 1. There's a King of Kings Somewhere, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. Bennie Knowles.
      - 2. A Charge to Keep I Have, 1942
      - 3. I'm Toiling, Lord, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06640b
      Performed by Alec Robertson.
      - 1. My Mind Done Changed, 1942
      - 2. Katy, I Got to Go, 1942
      - 3. Rock, Daniel, 1942
  - AFS 06641, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Alec Robertson and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the the Silent Grove Baptist Church in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06641a
      - 1. Run, Sinner Run, 1942
      - 2. There'll Be Preaching Tonight, 1942
      - 3. Outshine the Sun, 1942
      - 4. On the Other Side of Jordan, 1942
      - 5. Chariot of Jubilee, 1942
      - 6. The Band (Balm) in Gillian, 1942
      - 7. Hallelujah, 1942
      - 8. Keep a-Inchin' Along, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06641b
      - 1. Tell Me How Long Has the Train Been Gone (sanctified), 1942
      - 2. Cindy, 1942
      - 3. Interview about square dancing with Alec Robertson, 1942
  - AFS 06642, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Silent Grove Baptist Church in Clarksdale, Mississippi. Side B recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Friars Point, Mississippi.
    - Side A, afc1941002_afs06642a
      - 1. That's What's the Matter With the Church Today, 1942
      - 2. Clear the Line Before you Call, 1942
      - 3. My Mind Done Change, 1942
      - 4. Interview about old times in Hill house with Alec Robertson, 1942
    - Side B, afc1941002_afs06642b
      Performed by Annie Williams
      - 3. I Don't Care Where You Bury My Body, July 26, 1942
      - 4. Interview with Annie Williams, July 26, 1942
      - 5. Am I Born to Die, July 26, 1942
      - 6. Interview with Annie Williams, July 26, 1942
      - 7. There is a Fountain Filled With Blood, July 26, 1942
  - AFS 06643, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Friars Point, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      Performed by Annie Williams.
      - 1. Free at Last, July 26, 1942
      - 2. You Don't Believe I'm a Child of God, July 26, 1942
      - 3, Don't Grieve After Me, July 26, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Chicken Ma-Chaney-Crow, July 26, 1942
        Performed by Willie Moss.
      - 2. Tain't Gonna Rain No Mo', July 26, 1942
      - 3. When the Saints Go Marchin' In, July 26, 1942
      - 4. Sunday Mornin' Band, July 26, 1942
      - 5. Never Said a Mumbalin' Word, July 26, 1942
      - 6. Mary Mack, July 26, 1942
        Performed by Florence Mason, Emma Davis, Alice Austin, and Dorothy May Word.
      - 7. I Am a Funny Little Dutch Girl, July 26, 1942
      - 8. Chickama-Chick ma Chaney Crow, July 26, 1942
  - AFS 06644, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Shortenin' Bread, July 26, 1942
        Performed by Emma Jane Davis.
      - 2. Frog Went a-Courtin', July 26, 1942
        Performed by Florence Mason.
      - 3. Sally go Round the Sunshine, July 26, 1942
      - 4. Little Sally Walker, July 26, 1942
      - 5. Pullin' the Skiff, July 26, 1942
      - 6. Rock Daniel, July 26, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. Mason.
      - 7. Shout for Joy, July 26, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. A. Williams.
    - Side B
      - 1. All Night Long, July 26, 1942
      - 2. Dark Was Night, July 26, 1942
        Performed by John Cameron.
      - 3. Satisfy (dancing song), July 26, 1942
        Performed by Florence Stamp and group.
      - 4. Friars Point Victory Song (rope skipping song), July 26, 1942
      - 5. Ice-Cream, Soda Water (health song), July 26, 1942
      - 6. Milk, Milk (Hail, Hail, the Gang's all Here), July 26, 1942
  - AFS 06645, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Friars Point, Mississippi. Side B Track 2 recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Hiding Go Seek, July 26, 1942
      - 2. Hiding Go Seek, July 26, 1942
      - 3. Hiding Go Seek, July 26, 1942
      - 4. Come on, Boy, and Let's Go to Hunting (a local parody), July 26, 1942
        Performed by Flora L. Standifer.
      - 5. Jump, Mister Rabbit, July 26, 1942
      - 6. Mister Frog Went a-Courtin' in a Haystack, July 26, 1942
      - 7. Satisfy, July 26, 1942
    - Side B
      Performed by Minnie Lee Whitehead and Tommy "Jaybird" Jones
      - 1. Roustabout Songs and Reminiscences, July 26, 1942
      - 2. The Worried Life Blues, July 26, 1942
  - AFS 06646, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Shemod, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Test, August 4, 1942
      - 2. Levee Camp Holler, August 4, 1942
        Performed by Lewis Bell.
      - 3. I'm a Hard Working Daddy (levee holler), August 4, 1942
      - 4. Test, August 4, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Test, August 4, 1942
      - 2. Toast (You Shall Be Free), August 4, 1942
      - 3. T.P. Runnin', Smokestack Drag the Ground, August 4, 1942
      - 4. Hey, Hey, Captain (Levee Camp Holler), August 4, 1942
        Performed by William Henderson.
  - AFS 06647, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones in Shemod. Side B recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Tourist Camp in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Levee Camp Holler, August 4, 1942
      - 2. Hitler Toast, August 4, 1942
      - 3. Toasts, August 4, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Unloading Steel from Cars, August 8, 1942
        Performed by Houston Bacon and Elias Boykin.
      - 2. Sinking Rails, August 8, 1942
  - AFS 06648, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Houston Bacon and Elias Boykin and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Tourist Camp in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Spiking Down, August 8, 1942
      - 2. Shuffling Ties or Catching Ties, August 8, 1942
    - Side B
      - Shuffling Ties or Catching Ties (continued), August 8, 1942
  - AFS 06649, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Tourist Camp in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - Interview with Houston Bacon, August 8, 1942
    - Side B
      - Interview with Houston Bacon (continued), August 8, 1942
  - AFS 06650, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      Performed by Houston Bacon.
      - Lining or Calling Track, August 8, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Coon, Coon, Coon (I Wish My Color Would Fade), August 9, 1942
      - 2. Attitudes of White people towards Negroes, August 9, 1942
      - 3. Just Break the News to Mother (sentimental song), August 9, 1942
  - AFS 06651, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Will Starks and recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Tourist Camp in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Arkansas, August 9, 1942
      - 2. Interview with Will Starks about father, August 9, 1942
      - 3. The Late War, August 9, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Ollie Jackson, August 9, 1942
      - 2. The Travelin' Man, August 9, 1942
      - 3. The Fox Hunter's Song, August 9, 1942
  - AFS 06652, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Our Goodman, August 9, 1942
      - 2. Take a Whiff on Me, August 9, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Brady and Duncan, August 9, 1942
      - 2. Stackerlee, August 9, 1942
      - 3. Interview with Will Starks about the riverboats, August 9, 1942
  - AFS 06653, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Interview with Will Starks, August 9, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Down on the Farm, August 9, 1942
      - 2. Show me the Way to go Home, August 9, 1942
      - 3. I'm a Rowdy Soul, August 9, 1942
      - 4. My Old Mistis Promised Me, August 9, 1942
      - 5. Toast, August 9, 1942
  - AFS 06654, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. I'll Keep My Skillet Greasy if I Can, August 9, 1942
      - 2. The Dummy, August 9, 1942
      - 3. Didn't He Ramble, August 9, 1942
      - 4. Mister Grub Rice stops music - interview, August 9, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Buzzard Gets Rabbit in a Hollow Log, August 9, 1942
      - 2. Interview about ghosts, August 9, 1942
      - 3. Ollie Jackson, August 9, 1942
  - AFS 06555, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at Coahoma, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Hop, Brer Rabbit, in the Pea Vine, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Tuby Ford Smith and group of teachers.
      - 2. Hop, Brer Rabbit, in the Pea Vine, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. E.M. Davis and group of teachers.
      - 3. Hop, Brer Rabbit, in the Pea Vine, August 10, 1942
        Performed by group of teachers.
      - 4. Hop, Brer Rabbit, in the Pea Vine, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Dorothy Dilsewith Barry and group of teachers.
      - 5. We Go Logy, Logy, Logy, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Ruby Brown Hughes and group.
    - Side B
      - 1. Here Come Two Gents from Holland, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Ruby Harris and Ruby Brown Hughes.
      - 2. Bob-a-needle, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Dorothy D. Bawdry and group.
      - 3. Mister Frog Went to Courting, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Sara Lena Teague and group.
      - 4. We're Marching Round the Levy, August 10, 1942
      - 5. Down by the Green Apple Tree, August 10, 1942
      - 6. Who de Cat?, August 10, 1942
      - 7. How Many Miles to Bethlehem, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Florence Rembert and group of children.
  - AFS 06556, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Satisfy, August 10, 1942
      - 2. Satisfy, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Mabel Lou Brewer and group.
      - 3. Little Sally Walker, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Queen Esther Ivory.
      - 4. Uncle John's Old Rabbit, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Florence Rember(t?).
      - 5. Here Come Two Gentlemen from Holly Springs, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Queen Esther Ivory and Florence Rember(t?)
      - 6. Here We Go Loopy-ti-loop, August 10, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Mary Lou Brewer.
      - 2. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
      - 3. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
      - 4. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Ora B. Thomason.
      - 5. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Virginia Lee Thomason.
      - 6. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Louise Hicks.
      - 7. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Bill J. Lewis.
      - 8. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Flowers Lee.
      - 9. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
      - 10. All-Hid, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. E.M. Davis.
      - 11. Little Girl, Little Girls, August 10, 1942
      - 12. Little Girl, Little Girls, August 10, 1942
      - 13. Y Girls are High Minded, August 10, 1942
      - 14. Shortenin' Bread, August 10, 1942
        Performed by Billie James Levi.
  - AFS 06657, 1 16 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax and Lewis Jones at the Coahoma County Training School in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. All-Hid, August 11, 1942
        Performed by Ruby B. Hughes.
      - 2. Who-li-can, August 11, 1942
      - 3. Aunt Dinah's Dead, August 11, 1942
      - 4. Di Dee-o, August 11, 1942
        Performed by Ruby Harris.
      - 5. Shortenin' Bread, August 11, 1942
        Performed by Ruby Smith.
      - 6. Green Gravel, August 11, 1942
      - 7. All the Way Round, August 11, 1942
      - 8. How Many Miles to Bethlehem?, August 11, 1942
        Performed by teacher and group of children.
      - 9. Lost my Handkerchief Yesterday, August 11, 1942
        Performed by Willie Mae McReynolds.
      - 10. Sally Go Round the Sunshine, August 11, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Willy Over the Water, August 11, 1942
        Performed by Rosie Shelby.
      - 2. Needle Eye, August 11, 1942
      - 3. Shoo Fly!, August 11, 1942
      - 4. The Old Cow Died in Cool Water, August 11, 1942
      - 5. Chicken-ma-craney-crow, August 11, 1942
      - 6. Did You Ever See the Monkey Do the Motion?, August 11, 1942
      - 7. Chicken-ma-craney-crow, August 11, 1942
      - 8. Aunt Dinah's Dead, August 11, 1942
      - 9. Guessing games, August 11, 1942
        Performed by group of children.
  - AFS 06658, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Recorded by Alan Lomax at the Mississippi Baptist Convention in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - If I Be Lifted Up, 1942
        Performed by the choir of the Metropolitan Baptist Church.
    - Side B
      - 1. He Will Remember Me, 1942
      - 2. When I See His Precious Rainbow in the Sky, 1942
        Performed by unidentified woman.
  - AFS 06659, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - Where Shall I Go, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Every Time I Feel the Spirit, 1942
      - 2. There's No Hiding Place Down Here, 1942
  - AFS 06660, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. Piano Solo, 1942
      - 2. Wait a Little While, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Choir, 1942
      - 2. Hallelujah, 1942
      - 3. Does Anybody Here Know My Lord, 1942
  - AFS 06661, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    - Side A
      - 1. I Know I've Been Converted, 1942
        Performed by Mrs. Davis.
      - 2. I'm On A Shining Pathway, 1942
        Performed by Mr. Davis.
    - Side B
      - 1. I'm On A Shining Pathway (continued), 1942
      - 2. Interview with Thomas "Jaybird" Jones, 1942
  - AFS 06662, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Performed by Thomas "Jaybird" Jones and recorded by Alan Lomax at the Mississippi Baptist Convention in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - Interview with Thomas "Jaybird" Jones (continued), 1942
      - 1. Fo' Day Blues, 1942
      - 2. Ragtime tune (unidentified), 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Walking Billy, 1942
      - 2. Ragtime tune (unidentified), 1942
  - AFS 06663, 1 12 inch sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, mono.
    Side A and Side B Tracks 1-2 recorded by Alan Lomax at the Mississippi Baptist Convention in Clarksdale, Mississippi. Side B Track 3 recorded by Alan Lomax in Clarksdale, Mississippi.
    - Side A
      - 1. Interview with Thomas "Jaybird" Jones, 1942
      - 2. Interview with Thomas "Jaybird" Jones, 1942
      - 3. Interview with Thomas "Jaybird" Jones, 1942
    - Side B
      - 1. Corinna, 1942
        Performed by Thomas "Jaybird" Jones
      - 2. Angel Child, 1942
      - 3. I Heard the Voice of Jesus Say, 1942
        Performed by four girls.